boxing.com 2014-11-21

# Privacy and Terms of Use

At Boxing.com, we promise that your personal information is secure. Secure servers protect your information using advanced encryption and firewall technology throughout the ordering process. Please never send your credit card information via email.

We use 128bit encryption through SSL servers using Secure Certificates where required. Our servers are state of the art machines running the most recent versions Linux Operating Systems and Software. All security patches are updated regularily. We take internet security VERY seriously and make every effort possible to insure your credit card information and identity are protected.

**Privacy Policy**

Boxing.com is committed to our visitors and to protecting their privacy. We value our visitors and endeavor to create an enjoyable and valuable experience when visiting our network of sites. The following Privacy Policy applies to all visitors to the Boxing.com network of sites, and to all referrals made by our visitors.

**Customer Protection**

Boxing.com takes all measures to provide a safe environment with security procedures in place to ensure proper storage and careful retrieval of information so that nothing improper happens to your personal information while under our control.

**What we do with your information**

Your privacy is a very sensitive subject for us and we take it very seriously. So our privacy policy is simple: we will not sell, barter, give away or rent your personal information to any third party outside of Boxing.com, Inc. and its properties. Boxing.com may provide aggregate statistics about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information to reputable third parties, but these statistics will include no personally identifying information.

**Your consent**

By using our Web site and submitting your information to the Boxing.com network, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Boxing.com, Inc. If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. If you are not comfortable with any of the changes to our Privacy Policy, you will have the opportunity of un-submitting your information from our network at any time.

**Links**

Some sites within our network contain links to other sites. Boxing.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. If you have a question about the privacy policy of those web sites, please visit them directly.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, our site practices, or your personal experience dealing with this web site, you can [Contact](http://www.boxing.com/about) us.
